“Twenty years from now you will be more
disappointed by the things that you didn’t
do than by the ones you did do.
Sail away from your safe harbour.
Explore.
Dream.
Discover.”
Mark Twain.
Moving around has become very easy and comfortable.
Back to antiquity, people had to spend weeks,
months or even years before they arrived at
their destination.
At first, only wealthy people could afford
moving around for fun.
Now travelling has become an exciting challenge
for you and me!
Are you ready to take off?
“There is a whole world out there.
Pack your backpack, your best friend and go.”
Travelling with friends can help extend the
good times.
A hop-on hop-off tour bus ensures you will
see the most popular attractions.
Have you ever heard of museums in the eyes
of teenage visitors?
There are some awesome trip activities,
and … there may be a theme park.
The costs of things like rooms and transport
can be shared.
But when a trip isn’t organised well …
people waste time and money
people get nervous
things go wrong.
Avoid things that can go wrong
and plan your trip carefully.
So …, do you want to have an unforgettable
trip?
Moving around is here to help you.